Just another period western meta comedy short film.
The Gunfighter is a comedy, western film directed by Eric Kissack.
In the tradition of classic westerns, a narrator sets up the
story of a lone gunslinger who walks into a saloon.
However, the people in this saloon can hear the narrator and the
narrator may just be a little bit bloodthirsty.
Gunfighter, played by Shawn Parsons.
Tommy Henderson, played by Scott Beehner.
Johnny Henderson, played by Brace Harris.
Sally, played by Eileen O'Connell.
Sam, played by Jordan Black.
Bill Jessup, played by Timothy Brennen.
The Gunfighter is a 2014 short film directed by Eric Kissack.
A twist on the Western genre, the film concerns a group of people in a saloon who, in an
act of breaking the fourth wall, are able to hear the narrator of the film.
The film explores themes of parody, breaking the fourth wall, short film.
The tone is lighthearted.